Guide to the Kermit Carlyle Parsons papers, circa 1945-1999
Parsons, Kermit Carlyle papers, circa 1945-1999
- Series V. Professional
  - Professional Organizations and Conferences
    - Proceedings of the Second Seminar on the Role of Transportation in Urban Planning, Development, and the Environment, 11/1/1976 (Box 107, Folder 33)
    - Back to the City Conference, Washington, D.C., November 11-14, 1976 (Box 107, Folder 34)
    - National Growth Policy, 1975-1976 (Box 107, Folder 35)
    - National Growth Planning Panel (Transcripts), June 1976 (Box 107, Folder 36)
    - Washington DC Metropolitan Area Today - ULI 1976 Spring Meeting, 1976 (Box 107, Folder 37)
    - ULI Meeting Correspondence, 1976 (Box 107, Folder 38)
    - Conference files, notes, and correspondence, 1969-76 (Box 107, Folder 39)
    - Conference Maps and Brochures, 1977 (Box 107, Folder 40)
    - ASCP Conference, April 1977 (Box 107, Folder 41)
    - Biennial report of the State of Ohio, Board of Examiners of Architects, 1978 (Box 107, Folder 42)
    - KCP AICP Certification, 1978 (Box 107, Folder 43)
    - 5th Triennial Conference of Iaup - Conference agenda, 1978 (Box 107, Folder 44)
    - ULI Conference program, 1978 (Box 107, Folder 45)
    - Architects Review and other brochures., 1978 (Box 107, Folder 46)
    - NCARB test grader's manual, 1978 (Box 107, Folder 47)
    - Urban Land news and trends in land development, 1978 (Box 107, Folder 48)
    - Miscellaneous Notes, 1971-78 (Box 107, Folder 49)
    - SAH Annual Meeting, 1979 (Box 107, Folder 50)
    - SOM dinner, NYC, 1979 (Box 108, Folder 1)
    - International Symposium on Islamic Architecture and Urbanism, January 1980 (Box 108, Folder 2)
    - Architectural Archives Conference, 1981 (Box 108, Folder 3)
    - Professional Org. Certificates, clippings, 1953-1981 (Box 108, Folder 4)
    - International work in Korea, 1981 (Box 108, Folder 5)
    - NYS Committee on Housing 1982-83 Annual Report, 1982-1983 (Box 108, Folder 6)
    - The Pritzker Prize - IM Pei, 1983 (Box 108, Folder 7)
    - California Notes, 1984 (Box 108, Folder 8)
    - Affordable Housing Conference, Albany, New York, 1982-1984 (Box 108, Folder 9)
    - Willard conference, 1987 (Box 108, Folder 10)
    - Greenbelt conference, 1987 (Box 108, Folder 11)
    - Misc. Papers for Conferences, 1981-1988 (Box 108, Folder 12)
    - Papers for public presentation, 1968-1990 (Box 108, Folder 13)
    - Agenda: The Future of the Industrial City, 1990 (Box 108, Folder 14)
    - ULI Correspondence, 1990 (Box 108, Folder 15)
    - Holy Cross Lecture, 1989-1991 (Box 108, Folder 16)
    - ARHUS School of Architecture correspondence, 1993 (Box 108, Folder 17)
    - 36th Annual ACSP Conference Files, 1994 (Box 108, Folder 18)
    - Philadelphia ULI Housing Files, 1995 (Box 108, Folder 19)
    - The American University, '1995 (Box 108, Folder 20)
    - Phillipine Institute of Architects presentation, 1995 (Box 108, Folder 21)
    - Philippines Institute of Architects National Convention, 1996 (Box 108, Folder 22)
    - Philippines Institute of Architects National Convention, 1996 (Box 108, Folder 23)
    - Philippines Institute of Architects National Convention, 1996 (Box 108, Folder 24)
    - Planning Capital Cities Conference, 1996 (Box 108, Folder 25)
    - Gerhard Fehl Correspondence, 1995-1996 (Box 108, Folder 26)
    - Gerhard Fehl Correspondence, 1995-1996 (Box 108, Folder 27)
    - Gerhard Fehl Correspondence, 1995-1996 (Box 108, Folder 28)
    - Society for American City and Regional Planning History (SACRPH) - correspondences, 1998 (Box 108, Folder 29)
    - Society for American City and Regional Planning History (SACRPH) - correspondences, 1998 (Box 108, Folder 30)
    - Society for American City and Regional Planning History (SACRPH) - articles and correspondence, 1998 (Box 108, Folder 31)
    - APA National Planning Conference, Boston, 1998 (Box 108, Folder 32)
    - "From Garden Cities to Green Cities and Beyond" symposium, 1998 (Box 108, Folder 33)
    - American Society of Collegiate Planners Conference, 1998 (Box 108, Folder 34)
    - Garden Cities conference; and CSS book marketing, 1998 (Box 108, Folder 35)
    - Garden Cities and Ebenezer Howard seminar notes and overheads, 1993-1998 (Box 108, Folder 36)
    - "From Garden Cities to Green Cities and Beyond" symposium, September 1998 (Box 108, Folder 37)
    - files on GC to GC conference, 1998 (Box 108, Folder 38)
    - Garden City to Green City Symposium Files, 1998 (Box 108, Folder 39)
    - Correspondence for Garden City to Green City Symposium, 1998 (Box 108, Folder 40)
    - Garden Cities to Green Cities symposium handouts, 1998 (Box 108, Folder 41)
    - Garden Cities to Green Cities introduction, October 1998 (Box 108, Folder 42)
    - Garden Cities to Green Cities symposium wrap up, September 1998 (Box 108, Folder 43)
    - "Garden City to Green City" Conference Speeches and Introduction, July 1998 (Box 108, Folder 44)
    - Correspondence regarding GC to GC Conference, July 1,998 (Box 108, Folder 45)
    - Garden Cities Conference (Green to Green), 1998 (Box 108, Folder 46)
    - Garden Cities to Green Cities Seminar - Papers, Spring 1998 (Box 108, Folder 47)
    - Conference correspondence, 1993-1998 (Box 108, Folder 48)
    - Garden Cities to Green Cities correspondence, 1997-1999 (Box 108, Folder 49)
    - Garden Cities to Green Cities conference press release, 1998-1999 (Box 108, Folder 50)
    - Misc Professional, 1998-1999 (Box 108, Folder 51)
    - Manuscript: A vision of Green: Lewis Mumford's Legacy in Portland, OR, 1999 (Box 108, Folder 52)
    - Garden Cities to Green Cities, 1999 (Box 108, Folder 53)
    - ACSP: Baltimore Wars Abstract, 1999 (Box 108, Folder 54)
    - Garden Cities to Green Cities, Graham Foundation request and correspondence, 2000 (Box 108, Folder 55)
  - Professional involvement and history
    - Parsons' Daily Calendar, 1989 (Box 110, Folder 1)
    - Parsons' Daily Calendar, 1990 (Box 110, Folder 2)
    - Parsons' Daily Calendar, 1991 (Box 110, Folder 3)
    - Parsons' Daily Calendar, 1992 (Box 110, Folder 4)
    - Parsons' Daily Calendar, 1993 (Box 110, Folder 5)
    - Parsons' Daily Calendar, 1994 (Box 110, Folder 6)
    - Parsons' Daily Calendar, 1995 (Box 110, Folder 7)
    - Parsons' Daily Calendar, 1996 (Box 110, Folder 8)
    - Parsons' Daily Calendar, 1997 (Box 110, Folder 9)
    - Parsons' Daily Calendar, 1998 (Box 110, Folder 10)
    - Parsons' Daily Calendar, 1999 (Box 110, Folder 11)
    - KC Parsons Pocket Date Book 1950, 1950 (Box 111, Folder 1)
    - KC Parsons Pocket Date Book 1952, 1952 (Box 111, Folder 2)
    - KC Parsons Pocket Date Book, 1954-1955 (Box 111, Folder 3)
    - Parsons Miscellaneous Sketchbook, 1960 (Box 111, Folder 4)
    - KC Parsons Pocket Date Book, 1962-63 (Box 111, Folder 5)
    - KC Parsons Pocket Date Book, 1966-1968 (Box 111, Folder 6)
    - Parson's academic work schedule, 1969-1970 (Box 111, Folder 7)
    - Parsons Miscellaneous Notebook, 1971 (Box 111, Folder 8)
    - Parsons Date Book, 1976 (Box 111, Folder 9)
    - KC Parsons Pocket Date Book 1982-1983, 1982-83 (Box 111, Folder 10)
    - KC Parsons Pocket Date Book, 1990-93 (Box 111, Folder 11)
    - Parsons' Travel Diary, undated (Box 111, Folder 12)
    - Sketchbook, 1981 (Box 111, Folder 13)
    - Parsons Personal Notebook, 1993 (Box 111, Folder 14)
    - KC Parsons Pocket Date Book, undated (Box 111, Folder 15)
    - Parsons Contact Book, undated (Box 111, Folder 16)
    - KCP Schedules, 1963-64 (Box 111, Folder 17)
    - KCP Schedules, 1977-80 (Box 111, Folder 18)
    - KCP Schedules, 1970-86 (Box 111, Folder 19)
    - KCP Schedules, 1987-90 (Box 111, Folder 20)
    - KCP Schedules, 1991 (Box 111, Folder 21)
    - KCP Schedules, 1989-1992 (Box 111, Folder 22)
    - KCP Schedules, 1993-1994 (Box 111, Folder 23)
    - Map of the Travels of George Washington, 1931 (Box 112, Folder 1)
    - Analysis Dayton Population, 1948 (Box 112, Folder 2)
    - Architectural History course notes, 1948 (Box 112, Folder 3)
    - Parsons' Miami University Design Sketches and Notes, 1949 (Box 112, Folder 4)
    - Parsons CV and Biographical Data, 1949 (Box 112, Folder 5)
    - Residential design - articles and blueprints, circa 1950 (Box 112, Folder 6)
    - Mechanics (Miami University course, Max Mercer), circa 1950 (Box 112, Folder 7)
    - Commercial, work for Max Mercer - articles and blueprints, circa 1950 (Box 112, Folder 8)
    - Plans, Max Mercer office, circa 1950 (Box 112, Folder 9)
    - Parsons' Ohio State Board Architecture Exam Notes, 1951? (Box 112, Folder 10)
    - KC Parsons' Student Class Notes, 1951-1953 (Box 112, Folder 11)
    - KC Parsons Vitae, 1956-1966 (Box 112, Folder 12)
    - Cleveland Plain Dealer Article, K.C. Parsons, 1957 (Box 112, Folder 13)
    - Photocopy of Gary, Ind., 1959 (Box 112, Folder 14)
    - Parsons and Group Photo, 1959 (Box 112, Folder 15)
    - Ohio Seventh Annual Report, Roster of Registered Architects", 6/1/1962 (Box 112, Folder 16)
    - Parsons Curriculum Vitae, 1971 (Box 112, Folder 17)
    - Obituary for Anthony Adinolfy, 1971 (Box 112, Folder 18)
    - "Gamma Kappa Chapter - Theta Chi Fraternity at Miami University, Member Directory 1948-1972", 1948-72 (Box 112, Folder 19)
    - Syracuse AIA Training School, 1961-1974 (Box 112, Folder 20)
    - Photo of Parsons at SOM Dinner, 12/1/1979 (Box 112, Folder 21)
    - Harold C. Bernhard Memoirs (Addendum), 1980 (Box 112, Folder 22)
    - Parsons' Academic documents, 1981-1985 (Box 112, Folder 23)
    - 1984-1985 Parsons Calendar, 1984-1985 (Box 112, Folder 24)
    - Parsons Curriculum Vitae (Long and Short Versions), 1986 (Box 112, Folder 25)
    - Parsons' Biographical Material, 1987 (Box 112, Folder 26)
    - Santa Fe Opera event logistics, 1992 (Box 112, Folder 27)
    - Senior Cinema Photo Album. Parsons' 50th Reunion Lakewood High School Class of 1945, 1995 (Box 112, Folder 28)
    - Ithaca Commons - 20th Anniversary, 1995 (Box 112, Folder 29)
    - Schedules Programs (Kelly, Jones, Kahn), 1995-1996 (Box 112, Folder 30)
    - Transcript of Interview of Kermit C. Parsons by Bill Jenkins, 6/1/1997 (Box 112, Folder 31)
    - Aline M. Stein Obituary, 1998 (Box 112, Folder 32)
    - Parsons' CV and Cornell News Release, 2001 (Box 112, Folder 33)
    - Parsons Miscellaneous Notes, undated (Box 112, Folder 34)
    - Parsons Ohio Architect Stamp, Undated (Box 112, Folder 35)
    - Parsons' Student Notes- Architecture 220: 'History of Architecture', undated (Box 112, Folder 36)
    - Parsons Student Notes - Municipal Architecture, undated (Box 112, Folder 37)
    - Parsons Student Notes - Planning Design, undated (Box 113, Folder 1)
    - European Commercial Maps, undated (Box 113, Folder 2)
    - European Maps and Poster, undated (Box 113, Folder 3)
    - Travel Maps and Poster, undated (Box 113, Folder 4)
- Series VI. Multimedia
  - Garden Cities to Green Cities conference sessions, September 1998 (Box 115, Folder 1)
- Series VII. Oversize
  - "Living Units for Men: Cornell University", 1951 (Box 116, Folder 1)
  - Rand Hall, Sibley Hall Floor Plans, November 1974 (Box 116, Folder 2)
  - CRP Department Budget, 1977-1978 (Box 116, Folder 3)
  - Academic Wall Calendar, 1985-1986 (Box 116, Folder 4)
  - Cornell Academic Calendar, 1985-1986 (Box 116, Folder 5)
  - Academic Wall Calendar, 1986-1987 (Box 116, Folder 6)
  - Miscellaneous Building Files, undated (Box 116, Folder 7)
  - Notes on Cornell Agriculture Building, 1901-1912 (Box 116, Folder 8)
  - Cornell Campus Expansion 1892-1910 Files, 1892-1910 (Box 116, Folder 9)
  - A Half-Century at Cornell, A Retrospect: 1880-1930, prepared by the Cornell Daily Sun, 1930 (Box 116, Folder 10)
  - Miscellaneous Site Plans, undated (Box 116, Folder 11)
  - Miscellaneous Urban Sketch, undated (Box 116, Folder 12)
  - Project Improvements - Project I. Ithaca, NY, undated (Box 116, Folder 13)
  - Part I of the Center-Ithaca Urban Renewal Project prepared by Kelly, Parsons, Canfield & Stein, undated (Box 116, Folder 14)
  - Cumbernauld New Town: Preliminary Planning Proposals, First Addendum Report, April 1958 (Box 116, Folder 15)
  - Cumbernauld Technical Brochure (Box 116, Folder 16)
  - Cumbernauld New Town: Preliminary Planning Proposals, Second Addendum Report, January 1962 (Box 116, Folder 17)
  - Ithaca Financial Files and News Articles, 1964 (Box 116, Folder 18)
  - Legal data Notes, 1964 (Box 116, Folder 19)
  - Wayne County: The Aesthetic heritage of a Rural Area by Jacobs, 1979 (Box 116, Folder 20)
  - ULI Castro Valley Certificate, 1988 (Box 116, Folder 21)
  - University of IFE - Institute of African Studies, undated (Box 116, Folder 22)
  - Western Nigeria - University of IFE, undated (Box 116, Folder 23)
  - National Guide & Atlas of the Kingdom of Saudi Arabia, undated (Box 116, Folder 24)
  - Trinidad and Tobago 1975 Budget, 1975 (Box 116, Folder 25)
  - Trinidad and Tobago 1976 budget speech, 1976 (Box 116, Folder 26)
  - Trinidad and Tobago Supplementary notes on the budget for 1976, 1976 (Box 116, Folder 27)
  - Plans, drawing, and certificates (Mapcase-folder 2)